他去哪了
Where'd he go?!
我把他跟丢了
I lost him.
他好像从这里出去了
I think he went through here!
卡塞尔  趴到地上  快点
Castle, down on the ground, now!
你俩这是在重组
Are you guys re-enacting
"哼菩堤-蹬菩堤"罪案现场么
the humpty dumpty crime scene?
今天是秋分哎
It's the autumnal equinox today.
是啊  根据这位巫师先生的说法
Yeah, and according to Mr. Wizard there,
一年之中只有这一天
It's the only time of year
你能把鸡蛋给立起来
you can balance an egg on its tip.
-你们俩没正事儿可做么  -没
- Don't you guys have work to do? - Nah.
-嗯  没事做  -是么  那现在有了
No, not really. Hmm. Well, now you do.
还有  那什么把鸡蛋立起来的说法
By the way, that whole thing with the egg
-根本就是哄小孩儿的  -才不是
- Is just urban legend. - Not true.
去年我就看到卡塞尔做到了
I saw Castle do it last year.
哪壶不开提哪壶
What's wrong with you?
他还没和你联系么
Still no word from him?
没有
No.
也许你应该打电话给他
Maybe you should call him.
他自己说他秋天会回来的
He said that he would be back the fall,
现在秋天已经到了
and it's fall,
很明显他已经乐不思蜀了
so clearly, he has better things to do.
也许他还没从汉普顿回来吧
Maybe he's not back from the hamptons yet.
也许他的书还没写完
Maybe he's still working on his book.
是的
Yeah.
刚才还说到哼菩堤-蹬菩堤来着
Ooh. Speaking of humpty dumpty.
也许有人也想把她大头朝下倒立起来
Maybe somebody tried to stand her up on her head.
毕竟今天是秋分嘛
After all, it is the autumnal equinox.
她不是坠落致死的[fall亦有"秋天"之意]
It wasn't the fall that killed her.
她从上面那扇窗纵身跳下之前
More like multiple gunshot wounds to the torso
身体已经有多处中了枪
before doing a Greg Louganis out that window up there.
死者名叫克洛伊·惠特曼
Victim's name is Chloe Whitman.
几个行人听到枪声
Couple of pedestrians heard shots
然后看到尸体从窗口坠下
and saw the body fall out the window,
但是当警员赶到时
But when uniforms got here,
公寓空无一人
the apartment was empty.
也没有门卫当值
There's no doorman on duty,
所以目前为止  没人能回忆起
so, so far, no one recalls
见到任何人从现场逃走
seeing anyone flee the scene.
好的  让警员开始挨家挨户敲门询问
All right, have uniforms start knocking on doors.
看看还有什么是邻居们没有看见的
Find out what else our neighbors didn't see.
看  是卡塞尔耶
Hey, it's Castle.
看来他确实写完书了
Guess he did finish that book.
他寄本样书给我们会死啊
Nice of him to send us a copy.
看来他已经回到城里了
It looks like he's back in town.
他打个电话给我们会死啊
Nice of him to call.
行了吧你们俩
All right, guys.
别念念不忘你们的爱人了
You can stop pining for your girlfriend.
别忘了咱们面前还有具满身弹孔的尸体呢
After all, we got a body full of holes.
死者还有什么其他信息吗
So what else do we know about our victim?
她有个男友  名叫伊万·墨菲  他正在赶来
She's got a boyfriend. Evan Murphy. He's on his way.
好的  咱们上楼看看还有什么发现
Okay, let's go upstairs and see what else we can find.
他还真是全身散发着粗旷美
He really is ruggedly handsome.
唉
Mm.
从血的喷溅形状来看
From the spatter pattern,
她当时是背朝着门口的
she was backing away from the door.
中了第一枪以后  她试图逃开
After the first bullet hits her, she tries to get away.
但是除了跳窗以外无处可逃
Got nowhere to go but out the window.
大口径手枪
So large caliber gun.
子弹击穿了她的身体  然后打碎了玻璃
Round goes through her and breaks the glass.
接着她就从窗口跳了出去
She goes diving out.
看起来她正打算出城
Looks like she was leaving town.
这不是抢劫
Well, it wasn't a robbery.
麻烦你检查一下这些东西上面的纤维和指纹
Would you check these items for fibers and prints?
运气好的话  挣扎时会留下痕迹
If we're lucky, there was a struggle.
当然  包在我们身上
Sure. We'll take care of it.
贝克特  克洛伊的男友伊万来了
Beckett, Chloe's boyfriend Evan is here.
也就是说有人毫无缘由地
So someone just came here
来这儿朝她开了几枪
and shot her for no reason?
通常来说  这类案件总是会有原因可寻的
Well, usually, in cases like these, there is a reason.
你和惠特曼女士在一起多久了
How long had you and Ms. Whitman been dating?
大概六个月
About six months.
那她身边有没有什么人有暴力倾向
And was there anyone in her life with violent tendencies,
也许是某个和她发生过口角的人
maybe anyone that she had disputes with?
没有  她...
No. No, she...
我见她做过最坏的事就是乱穿马路而已
The worst thing I ever saw her do was jaywalk.
-她是做什么工作的  -她是个老师
- What did she do for a living? - She's a teacher.
她生前是个老师
She was a teacher.
大家都很爱她
They all loved her.
你本来是在等她今晚去找你吗
Were you expecting her over tonight?
-没有  怎么了  -她整理了一包过夜的行李
- No. Why? - Well, she packed an overnight bag.
这...这没理由啊
That-- that doesn't make sense.
她明天上午还要上课
She--she has class tomorrow.
她不会一个招呼都不打就离开的
She wouldn't just leave without saying anything.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
死者手里拿着这个
Victim had it in her hand.
她的手指把这个攥得太紧了
It was in her fingers so tight,
我差点就没看见
I almost didn't see it.
这地址在曼哈顿三角地
This is an address in Tribeca.
很可能就是她要去的地方
Could be where she was going.
只能去一探究竟了
Only one way to find out.
住在这里的人名叫玛雅·桑托丽
The address is registered to a Maya Santori.
32岁  背景干净  没有案底
32. She's clean. No priors.
-417号房么  -没错  就是这里
- 417? - Yeah, right there.
门开着
It's open.
纽约警察  举起手来
NYPD! NYPD! Let me see your hands.
-放下武器  -有枪
- Drop it, now! - Gun!
哇
Whoa!
卡塞尔
Castle?
贝克特
Beckett?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我...呃...
I... Uh...
放下  放下  把枪放下
Down! Down! Put it down!
立刻放下枪  你个白痴
Drop that gun now! Drop the gun, stupid!
-没事没事的  别担心  -放下枪  你个兔崽子
- Yeah, no, no, it's okay. - Drop it, scumbag!
伙计们  别紧张  事情不是你们想象的那样
Whoa. Okay, guys, easy. It's not what it looks like.
从来都不是  转过身去
It never is. Turn around.
卡塞尔  转过身去
Castle, turn around.
理查德·卡塞尔  你因为涉嫌谋杀被捕了
Richard castle, you're under arrest for murder.
感觉有点不一样了
Something's different.
你们重新装潢过了么
Did you remodel?
你知道你自己的权利了吧  卡塞尔先生
You've been informed of your rights, Mr. Castle?
你来真的啊
Really?
你都不打算问问我暑假过的怎样么
You're not even gonna ask me how my summer was?
你意识到你现在因为谋杀被捕了吧
You are aware that you're under arrest for murder?
我还以为你把我铐得那么狠是因为好玩儿呢
I thought you were being rough with the cuffs just for fun.
你气色不错
You look good.
你气色也不赖
You look good, too.
是嘛
Yeah?
-我说的是杀气  -你干嘛对我这么凶啊
- For murder. - Why are you so mad at me?
也许是因为我抓到你站在一具尸体旁边
Maybe because you were found standing over a dead body
手上还拿着一把枪吧
with a gun in your hand.
好吧  但是我告诉过你
Yeah, but I told you,
我到那儿的时候她已经死了
she was dead when I got there.
你为什么不打电话给我
Why didn't you call?
我正准备打电话给你
I was going to call you.
但还没来得及打  你已经到了
But then you showed up before I could.
是嘛
Really?
那你说说看
Well, then why did we find
你为什么会出现在死者的家里
you in our victim's apartment?
因为她打电话给我了
Well, because she called me.
噢  所以说你和桑托丽小姐正在发展关系
Oh, so you and Ms. Santori were in a relationship.
那可谈不上是什么关系
Well, I wouldn't say it was a relationship.
我从她那儿买了几尊雕塑而已
I bought a couple of sculptures from her.
你和她上床了么
Were you sleeping with her?
-这和案子有什么关系  -关乎动机
- How is that relevant? - Motive.
不  我没有和她上床
No, I wasn't sleeping with her.
你确定么  她那么漂亮的女人
Are you sure? Beautiful woman--
-我正进行着另一段感情  -和谁
- I'm in a relationship. - With whom?
-你换了口红么  -卡塞尔
- Is that a new lipstick? - Castle.
-你明知道是谁的  -我上哪知道去
- You know with whom. - How should I know?
我已经几个月没见你了
I haven't seen you in months.
这段时间里  你可能已经和若干个女人
You could've been in dozens of relationships
搞三搞四纠缠不清了
with women since then.
你这话醋味儿真浓
You sound jealous.
你和你前妻兼出版商约会
Jealous of you dating your
我吃哪门子醋
second ex-wife and publisher?
说说看
Tell me,
她是不是每件事都把你逼到"死"角
does she make you do everything on a deadline?
你又怎么样了
So how about you?
你还和你那个  呃  警察小男友在一起么
You still with that, uh, cop boyfriend of yours?
他叫啥来着  戴明
What was his name again-- Demming?
你们分手了
You broke up?
这个打电话给你的死者  电话里怎么说
This victim that called you, what was it about?
她说她遇到了麻烦
She said she was in trouble
但她不能去报警
and she couldn't go to the police.
那她为什么打电话给你
So why did she call you?
因为玛雅知道我和你有关系  噢
Because Maya knew I had a relationship with you--ooh.
是和纽约警局有关系
With the NYPD.
-她以为我能帮上忙  -怎么帮
- She thought I could help. - Help how?
这个她没说  她只是叫我过去
Well, she didn't say. She just told me to come over.
我到那儿的时候  门开着
When I got the, the door was open.
那地方一片狼藉
The place was trashed.
她被杀死在床上
She was dead on the bed,
地板上放着一把枪
and there was a gun on the floor.
你作为一个经常出入犯罪现场
So you, being the expert veteran of
经验丰富的老手
dozens of crime scenes,
竟然就这么捡起地上的凶器
decided to pick up the murder weapon to,
怎么  你是要确保我们有你的指纹么
what, ensure that we had your prints?
也许是你听漏了我刚才说的
Maybe you missed the part where
她被人开枪打死了
I said she was shot dead.
当我听到隔壁房间传来的动静
When I heard the noises coming from the next room,
我以为是杀死她的人又回来了
I thought whoever killed her was coming back.
于是我捡起枪用来自卫
So I picked up the gun to defend myself.
这个想法在当时的情境下无可厚非
It seemed like a very good idea at the time.
就在这时 你  埃斯波西多
That's when you, esposito and
还有安妮·欧克丽就撞门进来了
Annie Oakley come bursting through the door.
安妮·欧克丽
十九世纪闻名美国西部的女神枪手
Annie Oakley?
埃斯波西多警探的反应是出于...
Detective Esposito was responding--
我又不会威胁到你们
I am not a threat...
我差点就击中了卡塞尔
I kinda almost shot Castle.
谁让他手上有枪啊
What? He had a gun.
真该让你一枪毙了他
Shoulda let you shoot him.
这就是不打电话给我们的下场
It would've served him right for not calling.
我们现在应该在犯罪现场找线索才对
We should be at the crime scene looking for clues.
你说说看  我凭什么相信你
So tell me, why should I believe you,
别忘了
Considering that
你基本是靠编故事谋生的
you pretty much make up stories for a living?
因为你了解我啊
Because you know me.
你认识她吗  克洛伊·惠特曼
Do you know her? Chloe Whitman.
她被人开枪打死了
She was shot to death.
在她死后  我们在她的手心里发现了
Your friend's address was found in her hands
你朋友的地址
after she was killed.
又一起谋杀  她们俩有什么联系吗
Another murder? What's their connection?
我怎么知道  拿枪站在尸体边上的是你
I don't know. You were the one with the gun.
应该你告诉我才对
You tell me.
贝克特  过来说句话
Beckett, a word.
嗨队长  最近如何呀
Hey, captain. How's it going?
不是吧  你也这样
What? You, too?
搞什么...
Real--
别这样啊各位
Come on, guys.
鉴证小组复原了玛雅·桑托丽
C.S.U. Recovered the slugs
和克洛伊·惠特曼家里的弹壳
from Maya Santori and Chloe Whitman's place.
那枪是点45口径的
The gun was a .45.
卡塞尔的枪是点38口径
Castle was holding a .38.
也就说那枪确实是受害者用来自卫的
So it must have belonged to the victim for self-defense,
也就意味着卡塞尔说的是实话
which means that Castle was telling the truth.
但如果你想的话  我很乐意继续关着他
But I'd be happy to hold him if you like.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
这就没了
Well, that's it?
子弹和你的枪不吻合  你洗脱嫌疑了
Bullets don't match your gun. You're off the hook.
我...噢
I'm--ooh!
下一步干什么
So what's our next move?
没有下一步  有也没你份
There isn't one, at least not for you.
-你回家吧  -等等  等等
- You're going home. - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
两名死者  其中一个我还认识
Two victims, one of 'em an acquaintance of mine,
你竟然要我回家
and you're sending me home?
你是证人  卡塞尔  我不能让你参与
You're a witness, Castle. I can't have you involved.
-我已经参与了  -回家  卡塞尔
- I'm already involved. - Castle, go home.
回到汉普顿  回到你前妻身边
Go back to your Hamptons, your ex-wife,
开你的新书发布派对
your book parties.
我还有工作要做
Okay? I've got work to do.
我到底做错了什么
What did I do?
亲爱的
Darling!
你回来了  快来看看这个视频
Hello! Oh, you must see this video.
非常的...欠扁
It's absolutely... charming.
一个企鹅把另一只企鹅打到冰窟窿里去了
A penguin smacks another penguin into an ice hole.
我给你看看
I'll show you.
一会再说吧
Ah, maybe later.
看起来你像是被人打进了冰窟窿
Oh, you look as if someone smacked you into an ice hole.
我去局里了
I stopped by the precinct.
我以为你要等到巡回签售之后再回去的
I thought you weren't going back till after the book tour.
是啊  计划赶不上变化
Yeah, well, fate intervened.
-有个我认识的人今天被谋杀了  -天啊
- Someone I know was murdered today. - Oh, lord.
真是太可怕了  是谁啊
Dad, that's awful. Who?
玛雅  给我做那个雕像的女人
Maya. The woman who made that sculpture for me.
-有线索吗  -目前没有
- Any leads? - No, not yet.
大家过得如何
So how is everyone?
贝克特夏天过得愉快吗
Beckett have a nice summer?
大家都挺好的
Yeah, everyone's fine.
我可不信
Now why don't I believe you?
你周二不是会去切特那里吗
Aren't you with Chet on Tuesdays?
事情可不是一成不变的
Oh! That was never set in stone.
再说  阿丽克西斯有苦恼
Besides, Alexis is in crisis.
暑期培训认识的男孩
The young man from the summer program
还没有给她打电话
still hasn't called her.
尽管他说过他
Despite the fact he said we'd talk
从欧洲回来就会给我打电话  可他没有
when he got back from Europe, which he already did.
既然你知道他回来了
Well, if you knew he was back,
为什么你不打给他
why don't you just call him?
走的是他又不是我
He's the one who went away.
他要是在乎我  就会打电话了
I mean, if he still cared, he would've called.
也许他想打电话  但是
Maybe he was going to, but he didn't know
他不知道你的想法  也许他担心
how you'd feel about it. Maybe he was worried
在他走的这段时间事情有所变化
that something had changed while he was away.
理查德·卡塞尔
Oh, Richard Castle,
这是我听过最蠢的话了
that is the stupidest thg I ever heard.
关于感情这个问题我难道没教过你吗
Have I taught you nothing about relationships?
您老是个活生生的榜样
You're a shining example.
到底这个问题有多严重
Just how big a deal is this anyway?
我感觉我再也不想见到他了
I don't know if I even want to see him anymore.
拜托  你都没给他一次机会
Oh, come on. You're not even giving him a chance.
你为什么替他说话
Why are you siding with him?
我没有  我只是...也许他会
I'm not. I ju-- maybe he'll do something
想办法弥补的
that will make it right.
也许他会给你来个惊喜
Maybe he'll just-- maybe he'll surprise you.
也许他没这个机会了
Maybe he missed his chance.
要我说
If you ask me,
你应该把他关起来  出出这口恶气
you shoulda locked him up just outta spite.
不行  那样太缺德了
No, that'd be unethical...
不能放他去祸害那些拘留所的同事们
Making the people down in holding deal with him.
也是
True.
我滑...过头了
Hey. Whoa.
弹道科对比了两起凶杀
So... ballistics ran a comparison
留下的弹壳
of the slugs from the two murders.
出自同一把枪
They're from the same gun.
证人排查有线索吗
Anything on the canvass?
我们把克洛伊的照片
Well, we showed Chloe's photos
拿给玛雅的朋友和邻居看
to Maya's friends and neighbors.
他们不认识她
They don't recognize her.
而克洛伊的男友
And Chloe's boyfriend
以及她任教的高中的同事
and her colleagues from her prep school,
则根本不认识玛雅
They don't know Maya either.
好吧  被害人
Okay, so we've got...
是一位高中化学老师
a high school chemistry teacher
和一位雕塑家
and a sculptor
两人住址在市区的不同区域
who live on two different sides of town
根据大家的说法  生活完全没有交集
and by all accounts, run in completely different circles.
她们在同一天被杀
They're both killed on the same day
凶手又是同一个人
and by the same person.
她们的生活一定还是有交集的
The lives must intersect somehow.
好吧  查查电话记录和财务情况
All right, run phones and financials.
看看是否有线索
Let's see if anything pops.
这就去
On it.
我去蕾妮那看看
I'm gonna go and see Lanie
她有什么发现
and see if she's found anything.
莱恩等我
Ryan!
你好  LT
Hey, LT.
卡塞尔  你回来了
Hey, Castle. Back on the beat.
算是回来了  贝克特在吗
Yeah, looking that way. Is, uh, Beckett here?
她一个小时前刚检查完毕
Finished her sweep about an hour ago.
发现什么了吗
Did she find anything?
没什么有用的线索
Nothing useful.
我能进去看看嘛
Mind if I take a look around?
嘿  哥们
Hey, brother.
漏了一个地方
Looks like you missed one.
听说今天你逮捕了一名有趣的嫌犯
He I hear you made an interestingting arrest today.
想谈谈吗
You want to talk about it?
-不了  -好吧
- No. - Okay.
有心事不分享小心得溃疡
Keep holding that stuff in. You gon' get an ulcer.
有什么特别之处吗
Anything unusual?
你是说除了枪伤吗
You mean besides the gunshots?
我现在要找到
Yeah, I'm looking for anything
把两位被害人联系起来的线索
that will connect these two victims.
-她们都有纹身  -人人都有纹身的
- They both had tattoos. - Everyone has tattoos.
克洛伊·惠特曼  坠楼这位
Chloe Whitman, our jumper,
玫瑰图案
has a rose.
桑特瑞女士的后背上
And Ms. Santori has a mermaid...
则是美人鱼图案
on her back.
看上去是同一个人给她们纹上去的
Looking at the work, it could be the same tattoo artist.
还有其他线索吗
Anything else?
也许不是线索
It may be nothing,
但是我在惠特曼的手上发现了这个
but I found this on Ms. Whitman's hand.
2-2-7
也许是公寓的房号
Could be an apartment number,
健身房储物柜子号码  从褪色程度来看
gym locker code, and looking how faded it is,
-这是一周前写在手上的  -好的
- I'd say she wrote it about a week ago. - Okay.
对了  在桑特瑞女士口袋里有发现
Oh, and I found these in Ms. Santori's pockets.
出租车收据
Cab receipts?
一直到今天的  时间就在她死前几个小时
Dated today, just a few hours before she was killed.
我给出租车公司打电话
Okay, I'll call up the cab company,
看看能不能追查到她的去处
see if we can retrace her whereabouts.
你真不想和我谈谈
Are you sure you don't want to talk about it?
不想
Positive!
我们拿到了被害人的电话记录
We just got the phone records back on our vics.
原来她们有交集
Turns out they did have a connection.
她们死前不久都接到了同一个号码
They both received phone calls from the same number
打来的电话
within hours of their deaths.
能查到来源吗
Were you able to run it down?
找到了  这个人叫托德·麦卡奇
Yeah, it traced back to a Todd McCutchin.
他有抢劫和家庭暴力等前科
He's got priors including robbery and domestic assault.
-查到地址了吗  -那是当然
- You got an address? - Yeah, we got an address.
把手举起来
Let me see your hands!
我说把手举...
I said let me see your h--
是你们啊
Oh, hi.
我能解释的
I can explain.
转过身去
Turn around.
你就不能先听我解释一下嘛
Oh, would you just listen to me, please?
有什么可听的  你先不听话的
Why? Youu don't listen to me.
我只不过是自己在调查
Look, I was doing some digging around on my own.
-这又不算犯法  -没错
- That's not a crime, is it? - No,
但是非法闯入犯法  谋杀更犯法
but criminal trespassing is, and so is murder.
我只不过是想帮忙
I was just trying to help.
我不用你帮忙
I don't need your help.
你是怎么跑到这里的
How did you get here anyway?
-和你一样  我在追查一条线索  -是吗
- I was following up a lead, same as you. - Oh, really?
那么说你传唤了死者的电话记录
So you subpoenaed the victims' phone records
-找到了她们的共同点  是吗  -不是
- and looked for commonalities? - No, not exactly.
到底是怎么回事
Then what?
疼  好吧  告诉你  我反向查了电话号码
Ow! Okay! I star-6-9'ed. I star-6-9'ed.
-你反向查了电话号码  -用的玛雅的手机
- You star-69'ed? - Yes, on maya's phone.
我想反向查号码能得知最后的通话记录
I figured it would give me her last call.
电话拨到了麦卡奇这
It rang up McCutchin here.
在答录机上听到了他的姓氏
I got his name from his voice mail,
之后我就网上人肉他
And then I did a web search.
我厉害吧  崇拜我吧
Tell me you're not impressed.
未经允许你就进了正在调查的犯罪现场
You went to an active crime scene without authorization.
那个...
Uh...
是的
Yeah.
但是我戴手套了
But I wore gloves.
贝克特
Yo, Beckett.
尸体温度很低  应该死了很长时间
His body's cold. He's been dead for hours.
看吧  不是我杀的
See? I didn't kill him.
弹壳呢
Slugs?
还要查弹道
We'll have to run ballistics,
但是枪击伤口和前两位被害人身上的相同
but the entry wounds are the same size as our other vics.
奇怪
Odd.
-怎么了  -这小子修自动贩卖机的
- What? - Well, the guy's in vending machines.
看起来不像是能和
Not an obvious choice to be running around
艺术家和高中老师混到一起的人
with an artist and a prep school teacher.
是啊
Hmm.
让鉴证组到这里来
Okay, so let's get CSU down here
查找纤维和指纹
to look for fibers and prints.
再让他们查一查三个凶案现场的
And have them start looking for commonalities
共同之处
between the three crimscenes.
仔细查查他们的生活
Let's start digging into their lives.
哪怕用同一家约会网站
If they were on the same dating site,
也要让我知道
I want to know.
哪怕是他们一起参加自助培训
If they were in the same 12-step program,
也要让我知道
I want to know.
我能做什么
How can I help?
听着  卡塞尔  对于你朋友的死我很抱歉
Look, Castle, I'm sorry about your friend. I really am,
但是你不能像这样突然出现
but that doesn't mean that you can just show up
就好像什么都没发生一样
and act like nothing has happened.
事实上  如果你想回来
The truth is, if you wanted to come back,
早就回来了  但是你没有
you would've already, but you didn't.
我们面对事实吧
So let's just face it.
你之所以会在这里
The only reason that you're here right now
不过是因为
is because you were
你在错误的时间出现在了错误的地方
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
你有没有想过
You ever stop and think,
我也在等你的电话
maybe I was waiting to hear from you?
你知道这些命案意味着什么吗
Do you know what these bodies are?
-一个信号  -一个信号
- A sign. - A sign?
是的  是冥冥之中
A sign. A sign from the universe
命运告诉我们  我们应该一起办这个案子
telling us we need to solve this case together.
你不是想要和命运对着干吧
You don't want to let the universe down, do you?
不管我做什么你都不会走开  是不是
You're not gonna go away no matter what I do, are you?
人家看到信号了
I respect the universe.
好吧  算你狠
Okay. Fine.
我同意让你加入这个案子
I will let you join me on this one case
前提是你答应我  一切都听我的
as long as you promise to do what I say when I say it
不许再擅自调查了
and not to do any investigating on your own.
我保证  你不会后悔的
I promise. You won't regret this.
-已经后悔了  -现在开始吧
- I already do. - Starting now.
冰箱很吸引你吗
What is it about the refrigerator?
是因为它制冷  有光还是因为二者兼有
Is it the cold, the light or the combination of the two?
-睡不着  -因为那个男孩
- I can't sleep. - Ah, the boy.
-他终于来电话了  -很好
- He finally called. - Great.
-我没接  -为什么
- I didn't answer. - Why not?
我生气嘛  我以为他会留言的
I was mad. I thought he'd leave a message,
可他没留  我该怎么办
But he didn't. So now what do I do?
他知道我知道他打电话了
He knows I know he called.
但是如果马上我打回去
But if call back right away,
那就会显得我是在等他的电话
Then clearly I'm admitting I was waiting for his call.
我要等多长时间才能回电话
How long do I need to wait to call him back,
一天吗  半天还是两天
A day, at least a day, maybe two?
也许你应该换个新男友  重新开始
Maybe you should get a new boyfriend and start over.
碰着这种问题你也没辙了  是吧
You're not very good at this, are you?
明显没辙
Apparently not.
查到什么吗
Anything?
我们找到了托德·麦卡奇的未婚妻
Uh, we tracked down Todd Mccutchin's fiance.
她正赶过来
She's on her way.
有没有搜索到什么可疑的背景资料
You find anything in their background checks?
我们一直查到了小学
Well, we went as far back as grade school,
但没发现任何可疑的地方
and nothing has popped yet.
嗯  也许他们是中央情报局的高级特工
Hmm. Maybe they're top CIA agents
鸟尽弓藏兔死狗烹了
targeted for termination, huh?
你还真是三句不离中情局啊
CIA's a popular theory with you.
是啊  照常理来讲
Yes, well, law of averages demands
我一般最终都是是对的
that I'll eventually be right.
我都忘了您的高见是有多重要了
I've forgotten how helpful your insights can be.
哦  是吗
Oh, yeah?
打赌我比你先解决疑团
I bet I figure out how they're connected before you do.
行  我就跟你赌
All right. You're on.
但如果我赢了  你得保证走的远远的
But if I win, you have to promise to go away
从此不再插手我的案子
and never interfere with any of my cases again.
没问题  若我赢了
Fine. And if I win...
-就让我重新做你的搭档  -成交
- You have to take me back as your partner.  - Deal.
万一被他们先发现呢
What if they figure it out first?
-不可能  -不可能
- Nah.  - Nah.
你们两个在嘀咕什么呢
What are you two talking about?
卡塞尔在为没打电话过来而道歉
Castle was just apologizing for not calling.
你们有什么发现没有
So what'd you guys find?
从卡塞尔在玛雅的公寓
Forensics on that blood smear
发现的血液涂片的取证看来
that castle found in Maya's apartment--
和托德·麦卡奇的血型吻合
It's a match to Todd Mccutchin's.
鉴证组在玛雅的鞋上
And C.S.U. Found some of
找到了几滴麦卡奇的血迹
Mccutchin's Blood on Maya's shoes.
也就是说你朋友在他被杀之时或事发后
Which means that your friend was at his place
去过他家
either during or after the murder.
我查了一下她口袋里的的士票据
Ran down those cab receipts from her pocket.
根据出租车公司的记录  她昨天早上
According to the taxi company, they picked her up
在麦卡奇的公寓外面上了车
outside Mccutchin's apartment yesterday morning,
然后去了包厘街的某处
took her somewhere in the bowery.
包厘街
The bowery?
没错  20分钟后
Yeah. Then 20 minutes later,
她又坐车回家去了
they picked her up and they dropped her off at home.
就是在那之后她给我打的电话
It was just after that that she called me.
贝克特  麦卡奇的未婚妻到了
Beckett, Mccutchin's fiance is here.
抱歉  我从未见过她们
I'm sorry. I've never seen them before.
-你确定吗  - 你未婚夫有过作案记录
- Are you sure?  - Your fiance had a record.
有没有可能他在干一些
Is it possible he was involved in...
违法的事呢
uh, anything illegal?
托德是个好人
Todd was a good man.
我知道他以前做过一些坏事  但
I know he did some bad things in the past, but...
他有了自己的事业
He got himself his own business.
现在绝对是个合法商人
He was totally legit now.
不过
Only...
不过什么
Only what?
几个月前
A couple months ago,
托德弄伤了后背  不能做事了
Todd hurt his back and couldn't work.
银行要没收他的机器  所以
The bank wanted to take away his business, so...
他去找一个邻居
He borrowed some money
借了一笔钱
from a guy in the neighborhood.
那个人
This guy...
不是什么好人
He's no good.
他有威胁托德吗
Did he threaten Todd?
托德在努力还钱  但没有按期还清
Todd was making payments, but he fell behind.
几个星期前
A couple weeks back,
那个人拿着把枪到我们家来
the man came to the house with a gun.
他说若托德不还回欠款的话
He said he was gonna kill Todd
就要杀了他
if he didn't pay back what he owed.
我是借钱给他了  15000美元  有问题吗
I loaned him money. 15 g's. So what?
卡宾诺先生  有目击者说
Mr. Carbino, we have a witness
-你曾威胁要杀了他  -又怎样呢
- who says that you threatened to kill him.  - So?
结果他现在死了
So now he's dead.
不用你说  我自己看得到
Yeah, I could see that.
听着警探小姐  首先
Look, detective, first off,
15000美元不值得我去杀人
15 g's is not an amount of money worth killing for.
除非是到了穷途末路的时候
Not unless you've exhausted other avenues,
但我没有
to which I had not.
其次  更重要的是
And secondly, and more to the point,
你们的死者
your boy here,
已经连本带利的把钱还给我了
he paid me back the entire sum plus interest.
你以为我会信吗
Do you really expect me to believe that?
我知道你不会  宝贝
No, I don't, sweetheart.
但事实就是如此
But that don't mean it ain't true.
他的不在场证明已经核实了
His alibi checks.
他昨天一天都在新泽西州
He was in Jersey all day yesterday,
和情人在短山市购物
shopping at Short Hills with the missus.
哇  多幸运的女孩啊
Wow, lucky girl.
那也不代表不是他干的啊
Doesn't mean he didn't do it.
他可以雇个杀手
He coulda hired someone.
是可以雇杀手干掉麦卡奇
Yeah, to kill Mccutchin,
但为什么连玛雅和克洛伊也要杀呢
but why Maya and Chloe?
也许他们目睹了杀人现场
Maybe they witnessed the hit.
或者是他们联合贷的款
Maybe they cosigned the loan.
有麦卡奇的财务报表吗
Do we have Mccutchin's financials?
很快就可以找到  要那个干嘛
Yeah, they should all be up shortly. Why?
因为卡宾诺说
Uh, well, Carbino said that, uh,
麦卡奇已经把钱连本带利全还给了他
Mccutchin paid off his debt in full plus interest.
我在想  对于经营自动贩卖生意的人来说
I was just thinking, that's a lot of money...
那可是一个不小的数目
for a guy in the vending machine business.
我就怀疑
And I thought,
他从哪儿弄的钱呢
maybe, where did that money come from?
知道吗
You know,
麦卡奇的所有帐户都透支了
all of Mccutchin's accounts were overdrawn,
但两周前
and then suddenly, 2 weeks ago,
突然有了9500美元的存款进账
$9,500 appears in his savings.
两周前
Two weeks ago?
对  是  7号
Yeah. On the, uh, the 7th.
在同一天
There was a deposit
玛雅·桑托丽的帐户上
made in Maya Santori's account
也有同样多的钱进账
on the 7th for the same amount.
克洛伊·惠特曼呢
What about Chloe Whitman?
7号存款9500美元
$9,500 deposited on the 7th.
也就是说
Which means they were
他们有相同的资金来源
all receiving money from the same source.
而且花在同一个地方
And spending it in the same place.
玛雅·桑托丽和克洛伊·惠特曼
Both Maya Santori and Chloe Whitman
都曾在一个名叫
had charges on their credit card
K.C.B.C.的地方用信用卡消费过
for a place called K.C.B.C.
都是9号和16号去的
Both of them on the 9th and the 16th,
而且都只有少量消费  不到20美元
Both of them small amounts, less than 20 bucks.
麦卡奇也是
Same thing with Mccutchin.
那是他们碰面的某个餐厅吗
The restaurant where they met?
好了  给银行打个电话
All right, call up the bank.
看能不能帮忙查到
Let's see if they can help us track
是谁给他们存的钱
who made those deposits.
还要去联系一下信用卡公司
And I'd like to contact the credit card company
查一下这个 K.C.B.C.到底是什么地方
to find out what this K.C.B.C. Is.
马上去办
On it.
别以为这样就算你赢了
Don't think that this means that you won the bet.
我们只知道他们之间有关联
All we know is that they are connected.
但还不知道是何种关联
We still don't know how.
人家也很想你
I missed you, too.
嘿
Hey.
坏消息  根据银行记录
Bad news. According to the banks,
被害者是用现金进行存款的
our victims' deposits were made in cash.
不可能查到支付信息
There's no way to trace the payments.
而且由于存款不足10000美元
And since the deposits were less than $10,000,
所以也没有上报国税局
there was no report made to the I.R.S.
也就是说被害者们
Which means that our victims
很有可能在进行某种非法活动
were most likely involved in something iegal.
正如你所说的  从"被枪杀"的事实中也可看出
Just so you know, I got that from "Shot to death."
然后呢
So?
然后
So...
哪些不法活动要用到自动贩卖机
What illegal activity involves vending machines,
-艺术家和高中老师呢  -谁知道呢
- an artist and a high school teacher?  - I know.
就连我脑袋里
Even the stuff I'm making up
编的那些理论都讲不通了
in my head doesn't make sense.
我和信用卡公司谈过了
I talked to the credit card companies.
K.C.B.C.通过
K.C.B.C. Bills through
网上付款的方式受理账单
an internet card processing service.
没有文档记录
There's no address on file.
不能追踪网址吗
We can't even track it down?
我可没那样说
I didn't say that.
虽然没有文档记录
There's no address on file,
但每次刷卡交易
but they do register the I.S.P.
都有进行网上注册
of every swiped card transaction that goes through.
所以我让技术员进行了追踪
So I had tech track it down.
收款人是在这里进行操作的
Whoever ran those charges did it from this address.
我来就行了
I got this.
卡塞尔  上路
Castle, road trip.
谢你了
Uh, thank you.
你确定是这里吗
You sure this is the place?
你问我我问谁去
As sure as you are.
这里可不像是刷卡消费的地方
This doesn't look like a credit card kind of place.
而更像是
This looks more like
劫匪犯案的好据点
a "Get shot and robbed" kind of place.
有这个
There's...
你在做什么
what are you doing?
克洛伊的手上有这个数字
That was the number on Chloe's hand.
她来过这里
She was here.
这里  简直就是供应酒水的马戏团啊
This place--it's like the circus with alcohol.
我怎么以前从没来过呢
How have I never been here before?
这就让你兴奋了吗
You think this is crazy,
你该见识一下我曾经去过的俱乐部
You should see some of the clubs I've been to.
需要点什么
What can I get you?
信息
Information.
你认识这几个人吗
Do you recognize these people?
他们是凯蒂滑稽剧团的成员
Yeah. They're part of Kitty's burlesque troupe.
凯蒂滑稽剧团
Kitty's troupe
凯蒂·加那利  她是这里的老板
Kitty Canary. She runs the place.
在哪儿能找到凯蒂呢
And where can I find this this Kitty?
他们真的死了吗
They're really dead?
是的
I'm afraid so.
你们这儿的酒保说
Your bartender said that
他们是你剧团的成员
they were a part of your troupe.
克洛伊有时候会跳舞
Chloe would dance from time to time.
-托德有训蛇表演  -玛雅呢
- Todd had a snake act.  - What about Maya?
她算得上是老顾客
She was more of a patron.
是来寻找灵感的
She came for inspiration.
嘿  我刚听说了
Hey, I just heard.
警探  这是我丈夫厄尔
Detective, this is my husband Earl.
他和我一起管理剧团
He runs the burlesque with me.
你们知道是怎么回事吗
Do you know what happened?
我们正在调查
We're looking into it.
我们只知道他们都来过这里
the only connection that we can find is this club.
你不会认为是这里的人
Well, you don't think someone
杀了他们吧
here killed them?
你对他们了解多少
How well did you know them?
他们是工作伙伴
They were work friends.
只是点头之交而已
You know, "Hi, how are you?"
不过玛雅和克洛伊曾来过店里
Although Maya and Chloe did come to the shop once
做纹身
to get tattoos.
那是我白天的工作
My day job.
他们三个经常在一起吗
Did the three of them spend a lot of time together?
没有经常在一起  和其他人差不多
No more so than anybody else.
这里有谁和他们来往比较密切的吗
Did they spend a lot of time with anyone else here?
我没看到
Not that I noticed.
你们有常客的电子名单吗
Do you have a mailing list of your regulars?
-有  我可以给你一份  -谢谢
- Yes. I can get a copy if you want.  - Yes,
我还需要一份这里所有员工
and I'll also neea list of all of your employees
以及剧团其他人员的名单
and any other members of your troupe.
-没问题  -你能想到他们三个之间
-Of course.  -Can you think of any other connection
除此之外的其他关联吗
between the three of them?
曾经 曾经发生过一件事
Well, there w-- there was the incident.
几个星期前
A couple of weeks ago,
克洛伊的男朋友来过
Chloe's boyfriend came around.
很显然  他不喜欢她在这里跳舞
Apparently, he didn't like her dancing here.
他的反应有点激烈
He got a little rough.
玛雅和托德都插手了
Both Maya and Todd intervened.
伊万喝醉了
Evan was drunk,
说了很多疯话
Yeiling all kinds of crazy stuff.
什么话
What kind of stuff?
我知道你在做什么  我清楚得很
"I know what you're doing. I know all about it."
我猜他是以为她在和别人乱搞
I guess he thought she was screwing someone else.
好吧  那天晚上我是跟踪克洛伊到俱乐部去了
Okay, so I followed Chloe to the club that night,
那是因为她那时候行为怪异  很神秘
But only because she was acting weird, secretive,
我以为她在和别人约会
And I thought she was seeing another guy.
墨菲先生  为什么之前你没说呢
Mr. Murphy, why didn't you tell us this before?
说我和女朋友吵过架
That I'd been fighting with my girlfriend,
还威胁过她  我很清楚警察是怎么办案的
that I'd threatened her? I know how cops work.
当你发现其他死者
And when you found out about the other victims,
也都是俱乐部成员时呢
that they were all there at the club?
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her.
我没有杀害任何人
I didn't kill any of them.
要是你会怎么做
What would you have done?
我会找出杀人凶手
I would try to help find her killer.
若我那时告诉你们这件事
But if I had told you then what you know now,
你们还会怀疑其他人吗
would you have looked any further than me?
墨菲先生  克洛伊账上的钱
Mr. Murphy, the money in Chloe's account,
是从哪儿来的
where did it come from?
什么钱
What money?
他承认有过争吵和威胁
So he admits to the fights and the threats,
但却坚持对钱的事一无所知
but he claims not to know anything about the money...
也否认知道死者除了那天晚上的事之外
Or how our victims are connected
还有什么别的关联
other than the events of that night.
你相信他吗
Do you believe him?
我怎么想不重要
It doesn't matter what I believe.
他是嫌疑犯  嘿  莱恩
He's a viable suspect. Hey, ryan.
我要你去申请一张
I need you to get a search warrant
伊万·墨菲家的搜查令
for Evan Murphy's place.
还有  埃斯波西托  你那边怎么样
And, Esposito, how are things going over there?
我查了一下俱乐部名单里有前科的人
We ran the club's mailing list for people with priors.
暂时只查到这几个
These are the ones that have popped so far.
好  查一下他们和受害人有什么关系
All right, run 'em for any connections with our vics.
马上去办
Right on.
什么
What?
这张脸很眼熟
I've seen this guy's face.
是同一个人
That's the same guy.
玛雅认识他
Maya knew him.
兰德·道约尔
"Xander Doyle."
非法持枪罪  意图散布武器
Weapons charges, conspiracy to distribute,
而且很明显  他住在包厘街
And apparently, he lives in the bowery.
我敢打赌
How much you want to bet
玛雅在麦卡奇被杀后
Maya was on her way to see him
正要去见道约尔
after Mccutchin's murder?
对  当然  我认识玛雅
Yeah, sure. I knew Maya.
我们几个月前在俱乐部认识
I met her at the club a few months back.
你们是什么关系
and what was the nature of your relationship?
她说她喜欢我的样子
She said she liked the way I looked.
接下来你也猜得到
You know how it goes.
你最后一次见到她是什么时候
When was the last time you saw her?
道约尔先生  我们有证据显示
Mr. Doyle, we have evidence that indicates
玛雅死的那天曾和你见过面
That Maya came to see you the day she died.
她说她有麻烦了
Look, she said she was in trouble.
-她需要我的帮助  -什么样的麻烦
- She needed my help. - What kind of trouble?
她不肯说
She wouldn't say.
一定是有人在找她麻烦
Someone must have been after her.
为什么这样说
And why would you say that?
因为她来找我的原因
'cause the reason she came to see me is,
是因为她要借枪
she wanted to borrow a gun.
这能解释为什么她有武器
that's why she was armed.
她看见麦卡奇的下场
She saw what happened to Mccutchin.
认为下一个就到自己
She figured she'd be next.
道约尔先生  有任何迹象表明
Mr. Doyle, did Maya give you any indication
玛雅可能卷入什么事情吗
As to what she might have been involved in?
没有  如果让我猜的话
No. If I was a betting man...
几周前我在街上遇见玛雅
I ran into Maya a few weeks ago on the street.
她给了我一个拥抱  我闻到了
She gave me a hug. I could smell it.
你闻到什么
You could smell what?
恶心的气味  涂料稀释剂  丙酮
That sick smell--paint thinner, acetone,
漂白剂  我有个兄弟闻起来跟她一样
bleach. I got a buddy who smells like that.
你知道他干什么的吗
You know what he does?
他制造冰毒
He makes meth.
这太明显了
it's so obvious.
我不敢相信我没早点想到
I can't believe I didn't think of it sooner.
你真的觉得是冰毒吗
Do you really think it was meth?
这是唯一合理的解释了
It's the only thing that makes any sense.
受害者全都有财政上的困难
All of our victims were struggling financially.
某天晚上  俱乐部关门后
One night after the club closes, they're all together
他们一起谈论缺钱的问题
Talking about their money woes
直到我们的高中化学老师开玩笑
Until our high school chemistry teacher cracks a smile
说  咱们随时可以自制冰毒嘛
And says, "Well, we could always make meth."
但其他人没有笑
But the others don't laugh.
他们说  对  我们可以做冰毒
They say, "Yeah, we could make meth."
就像那部电视剧一样[详见《Weeds单身毒妈》]
Just like that cable show.
听我的吧  就是毒品
I'm telling you, it's drugs.
-不是毒品  -你确定吗
- It's not drugs. - Are you sure?
是  那家伙说的化学物品是对的
Yes, and your guy was right about the chemicals.
我在三具尸体上都找到漂白剂
I found trace amounts of bleach, acetone,
丙酮  氯化钠还有氨的痕迹
Sodium chloride and ammonia on all three bodies.
你怎么知道这不是毒品
So how can you tell it's not drugs?
因为少了些东西
Because of what's missing.
如果死者想要在家烹制冰毒
If your guys had been cooking up meth
或者任何自制毒品
Or any other street-lab drugs,
一定会有其他的化学成分
There would be other substances present,
更别说会有一部分毒品成品的残余了
Not to mention the trace amounts of the finished product.
这说明  他们肯定在筹划什么
That being said, they finitely were up to something.
嗯
Hmm.
-贝克特  -嘿  我是莱恩
- Beckett. - Hey, it's Ryan.
伊万·墨菲家的搜查证
That search warrant on Evan Murphy's place?
没白申请
It paid off.
我们找到了凶器
We found the murder weapon.
我对天发誓  我从来没看见过这东西
I swear to god, I've never seen that before in my life.
那它为什么会在你家
Then what was it doing in your place?
-我不知道  -你跟踪克洛伊到俱乐部
- I don't know! - What really happened the night
那天晚上到底发生什么事了
that you followed Chloe To the club?
我告诉过你  我们吵架了
I told you, we fought.
为了什么  别说是因为外遇
About what? And do not say the affair.
你们四个到底在盘算什么
What were the four of you into?
伊万  你们是什么关系
Evan, what's the connection?
你为什么要杀他们
Why did you kill them?
我要律师
I want a lawyer.
律师来之前我什么都不会说
I'm not saying anything else without a lawyer.
律师办公室接到通知
P.D.'s office has been notified.
他们正派人过来
They're sending someone over.
通知地方检察官看能否帮我们和律师谈谈
Okay, notify the D.A. Maybe they can cut us a deal
让我们弄清楚到底发生什么事
and help us figure out what was really going on.
我知道这个表情
I know that look.
什么表情
What look?
"有点儿东西不对劲" 的表情
That "Something doesn't add up" Look.
凶器的实验室报告有点不对劲
It's just the lab report on the murder weapon.
怎么了
What about it?
他们找不到任何指纹
They didn't find any fingerprints.
他大概已经擦掉了
He probably wiped it down.
他既然把指纹擦了
Why would he wipe it down
那干嘛还要留着枪
if he was gonna hang on to it?
也许他想丢的
Maybe he was going to ditch it
只不过没找到合适的机会
but didn't get around to it.
他会做的第一件事就是把凶器丢掉
Ditching it would be the first thing that he would do.
或者他觉得还有用处
Maybe he thought he still needed it.
-再去杀人  -或者保护自己
- To kill someone else? - Or protect himself.
嘿  贝克特
hey, yo, Beckett.
伊万的财政报告出来了
Financials came back on your boy Evan.
沒什么异常账目
There's no unusual activity.
或者这就是动机
Maybe that was his motive.
不管他们在干什么
Whatever it was they were up to,
他没拿到钱
he didn't get his cut.
那些钱去哪里了
But what was his cut?
我是说  他们到底在干些什么
I mean, what the hell were they into?
这简直就是个冷笑话  雕刻家
It's like a bad joke-- a sculptor,
自动售卖机推销员和化学老师
A vending machine salesman and a chemistry teacher
走进一间滑稽剧酒吧
walk into a burlesque bar.
对  虽然这个笑话完全没有笑点
Yeah, only we don't have a punch line.
唯一的笑点就是
Other than they made
他们大赚一笔之后却有钱没命花了
a bunch of money and got themselves killed.
大赚一笔
"Made a bunch of money."
什么
What?
一个金属雕刻家  一个化学家
A sculptor who works with metal, a chemist...
还有自动售卖机技工
And a vending machine operator...
我想我知道受害者在干什么了
I think I know what our victims were up to.
克洛伊的钱包还在吗
Do we still have chloe's purse?
哇
Whoa.
你找什么呢
What are you looking for?
啊哈
Aha!
看一下这些钞票上的序号
Take a look at the serial numbers on those bills.
一模一样
They're the same.
这些钞票全是1998年之前的
These bills are all pre-1998.
就在货币被重新设计之前
That's before they redesigned the currency.
这就是笑点了
That's our punch line.
他们就是因此聚到一块儿的
That's how these people are connected.
在造假币的环节中
In counterfeiting,
最难伪造的就是纸张
the hardest thing to make is the paper.
但他们有足够的纸
But they had all the paper they needed.
他们有取之不竭的一块纸币
They had an unlimited supply of $1 bills.
从自动贩卖机里弄来的
From the vending machines.
那些受害者身上找到的化学物
And those chemicals we found on our victims' bodies...
是用来漂洗一元纸币
Were used to whitewash the singles
做成空白的钞票
In order to make blank bank notes.
这个步骤需要一名化学家
A procedure requiring the expertise of a chemist.
那他们用空白的钞票做什么
And what do counterfeiters do with blank bank notes?
印上更大的面额
Print larger denominations,
那他们就需要一个金属压板
For which they need a metal press plate.
没有比雕刻家更适合的了
And who better to provide that than a sculptor?
那么
So...
金属板  纸
Plates, paper...
只剩下一种原料了
There's only one missing ingredient.
-我知道谁是凶手  -我知道谁是凶手
- I know who the killer is! - I know who the killer is!
走吧
Let's go.
过来  快点
come on! Hurry up!
带上金属板  金属板
Get the plates! The plates!
要去哪里啊
Going somewhere?
把手举起来
Let me see your hands.
离开那些袋子  向前走
Step away from the bags and walk forward.
没错了  都是假的
Yeah, they're fake.
你们怎么怀疑我的
What gave me away?
缺少的原料
The missing ingredient.
墨水
Ink.
沒人比刺青师更适合提供墨水了
And who better to provide it than a tattoo artist?
还有伊万·墨菲
that and Evan Murphy.
你知道我们听到消息后会马上行动
You knew that we'd follow up after you told us that story,
于是你栽赃那把枪
So you planted that gun,
但你却不够时间
but you just didn't have enough time
印上他的指纹
to put his prints on it, did you?
-仔细搜查这里  -小心
- Sweep the area-- - Look out!
走  走  抓住他
Go! Go! Get him!
行动行动  快点
Move! Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
-凯蒂在哪里  -钞票没了
- Where's kitty? - The money's gone.
-你留在这里  -要是他们回来怎么办
- You stay here. - What if they come back?
嘿  嘿
Hey! Hey!
他在外面  你抓到他了没
he's out here. You got him?
他好像从这里走了
I think he went around this way.
看见他了吗
Do you see him?
我没看到  我没看到他
I don't see him. I don't see him.
快来  警察  警察
Come on! Police! Police!
卡塞尔  趴到地上  快点
Castle, down on the ground, now!
放下枪
Drop it. Drop it.
不许动  给我老实躺在地上
Don't move. Stay on the ground, right where you are.
转过来  呆在原地  别碰那把枪
Turn over. Stay where you are. Don't touch the gun.
有一晚他们在俱乐部想出这个计划
They hatched the plan late one night at the club.
他们以为这于人无害
They figured, victimless crime,
没人会受伤
nobody would get hurt.
凯蒂和厄尔利用俱乐部洗钱
Kitty and Earl would launder the bills through the club
然后用现金分赃
And then make cash payments to the others.
听起来是个不错的交易
It sounds like they had a sweet deal going on.
-哪里出错了  -托德·麦卡奇
- How'd it all go wrong? - Todd Mccutchin.
他用伪钞还债被发现了
He was getting squeezed by a loan shark,
放高利贷的人
figured he'd try to make a payment
借此趁机勒索他
with counterfeit bills.
威胁要供他出来
The shark threatened to rat him out
除非让他接手交易
unless he turned over the operation.
玛雅和克洛伊愿意
Maya and Chloe were willing,
但凯蒂和厄尔反对
but Kitty and Earl weren't.
托德跟他们对质
And when Todd confronted them,
他完全不知道自己惹上的是什么人
he had no idea who he was dealing with.
凯蒂·加那利  又名卡拉·布里泽
Kitty Canary, A.K.A. Carla Breezer.
曾在西雅图当脱衣舞女
She was a stripper in Seattle.
她曾因试图离开她的男友
She did a nickel for a manslaughter charge
被控过失杀人
for trying to run over her boyfriend.
出狱后
When she got out,
她换了名字  有了新男友
she got a new name, new boyfriend
甚至换了地方
And even changed coasts.
她不是那种乖乖让托德摆布的女孩
She wasn't the type of girl to let Todd take her down.
他们需要的东西都有了
They had everything they needed--
化学公式  金属板
The chemical formulas, the plates.
他们要做的就是摆脱其他人
All they had to do was get rid of the others.
你俩一搭配  果然干活就不累
Nice work, you two. Very impressive.
但我要你明天给我解释清楚
But tomorrow, I want you to tell me the story
卡塞尔是怎么拿到你的枪的
about how Castle got your gun.
那么  这回算你赌赢了
So, uh... I guess you won the bet.
是的
Yeah.
但说真的  如果你不想我...
But look, if you don't want me to--
不不不  你赢得正大光明
No, no, no. No. You won fair and square.
那么
So...
明天见
See you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow.
老实交代
So...
你比卡塞尔早多久
how long before Castle that
发现这案子是关于假钞的
you know this is about counterfeiter.
是那谁...
Is that...
对  她已经聊了一个多小时了
Yeah. She's been on the phone for over an hour.
-是谁先打给谁的  -这不重要
- So who called whom first? - What's it matter...
他们联络上了  这就足够了
as long as they connected.